To wrap up and summarize our discussion of the global analysis of control flow graphs,
为了总结和总结我们对控制流图全局分析的讨论，
we've talked about two kinds of analysis in the past several videos. Constant
在过去的几个视频中，我们已经谈到了两种分析。常量
propagation is what is called a forwards analysis Because information is pushed
传播是所谓的向前分析，因为信息被推送
from the inputs to the outputs. So if you think about a control flow graph. What
从输入到输出。所以如果你考虑一下控制流图。什么
happens in control flow analysis is that information flows in this direction.
在控制流分析中发生的情况是信息在这个方向上流动。
It flows in the same direction as computation. If I have a constant up here
它与计算方向相同。如果我这里有一个常量
x is assigned constant down here, and x is used later on and that constant will flow
x在这里被赋值为常量，稍后使用x，该常量将会流动。
forward to the uses. Okay So information flows in the same direction as computation.
展望未来的用途。好的，所以信息流动的方向和计算是一样的。
Liveness on the other hand is a backwards analysis. Information is pushed
另一方面，活跃度是一种逆向分析。推送信息
from outputs back towards inputs. So here in this example and let me change
从输出回到输入。所以在这个例子中，让我更改一下
colors. Here we see that x is live before the statement. And that liveness gets propagated
颜色。这里我们看到x在语句之前是活动的。这种活跃度就会被传播
in the other direction. It gets propagated against the control, against the
在另一个方向。它针对控件传播，针对
flow, of execution, backwards towards the beginning of the program.
执行流程，向后向程序开始的方向流动。
So they're many other kinds of global flow analysis in the literature. The
所以它们是文献中的许多其他类型的全球流动分析。这个
constant propagation analysis and the liveness analysis are two of the most important.
恒定传播分析和活性分析是其中最重要的两个。
There is a number of others that are also very important and many, many
还有一些其他的也非常重要，而且很多，很多
more that people have investigated. Almost all these analyses can be classified
更多的是人们已经调查过的。几乎所有这些分析都可以归类
as either forward or backward. There are some analyses and some important
不是向前就是向后。有一些分析和一些重要的
ones that are neither forward nor backward. That information is basically pushed
既不向前也不向后的。这些信息基本上是推送的
in both directions. And the other thing is that the, almost all the analyses
两个方向都有。另一件事是，几乎所有的分析
in the literature that do global flow analysis anyway also follow this methodology
无论如何，在进行全局流分析的文献中也遵循这种方法
of local Rules that relay information between adjacent program points.
在相邻节目点之间中继信息的本地规则。
So it, it's the local rules part that's important. So we break down the complicate
所以，当地的规定才是最重要的。所以我们把复杂的
d problem of analyzing an entire control flow graph into a collection
将整个控制流图分析为集合的三维问题
of rules that only do ver, propagate information very, very locally.
这些规则只会非常非常本地地传播信息。